Finding Aid for the War Relocation Authority Central Utah Project Topaz, Utah
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
War Relocation Authority Central Utah Project Topaz, Utah
1942-1945
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0489
.42 linear feet
Scope and Contents
- Brochures and/or Pamphlets
  - ‘Born Free and Equal’ by Ansel Adams, 1944
  - ‘The Displaced Japanese-Americans’ by American Council on Public Affairs, (1944)
  - ‘NISEI in Uniform’ by Department of Interior, (1943)
  - ‘Outcasts!’ by Caleb Foote, 1943
  - ‘What About our Japanese-Americans?’ by Carey McWilliams, 1944
  - ‘Without a Country?’ by Women’s International League for Peace and Freedom
- Magazine
  - TREK, June 1943
- Magazine Article
  - Developing World Citizens in a Japanese Relocation Center by Wanda Robertson, Childhood Education, October 1943
- Prints – 5
- Promotional Literature
  - Education in the Central Utah War Relocation Project
  - Welcome to Topaz